Luz Stella NIETO MANTILLA

Master II in Economics and Finance – University of Luxembourg

Highly professional Corporate Services assistant with a strong educational background in Economics and Finance, complemented by extensive administrative and financial experience. Knowledgeable in Luxembourg investment vehicle regulations, corporate documentation, and customer relationship management. Fluent in Spanish, English and French; proficient in Luxembourgish and German.



CONTACT

19 rue Émile Mayrisch L – 2141 Luxembourg +352 621 65 22 11 lsnm@outlook.com

Nationality: Luxembourgish -Colombian

Driving License B

LANGUAGES

Native Spanish **English Fluent Fluent** French Luxembourgish Intermediate

German **Basic**

FAMILIAR SOFTWARE

EViews (Past Use)

Stata (Past Use)

SOFT SKILLS

- Work under pressure
- Team spirit
- Attentive listener
- Sociability

INTERESTS

Writing, reading, sewing, knitting, crocheting, panting, dancing, walking, admire the beauty of nature

PROFESSIONAL COMPETENCIES

- ✓ Drafting legal documents
- ✓ Office Management
- ✓ Corporate Documentation
- ✓ Microsoft Office Suite (Latest Version)
- ✓ Ciel Compta, Avonca
- ✓ Legal Procedures
- ✓ Al Tools: ChatGPT

EDUCATION

2011	Master II in Economics and Finance
	University of Luxembourg, Luxembourg, (Luxembourg)
2003	Economics

Universidad del Atlántico, Barranquilla, (Colombia)

OTHER RECENT CERTIFICATIONS AND TRAINING

2022	Managing and calling investment and dusts
2023	Managing and selling investment products
	Life Long Learning Center, Luxembourg, (Luxembourg)
2018	Overview of Luxembourg company law
	Life Long Learning Center, Luxembourg, (Luxembourg)
2013	Corporate Accounting
	Life Long Learning Center, Luxembourg, (Luxembourg)
2024	Luxembourgish, B1 (conversation)
	Institut National des Langues. Mersch, (Luxembourg)
2023	German, A2
	Institut National des Langues. Mersch, (Luxembourg)
2018	Luxembourgish, B1 (grammar)
	Institut National deal annual Lucianda com ()

Institut National des Langues. Luxembourg, (Luxembourg)

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

04.2018 - present **Creative Designer** Freelance Luxembourg, (Luxembourg)

Led knitting projects, managed individual orders, and

coordinate with workers.

04.2017 - 04.2018**Administrative Officer**

KRIEG & DUTA Law Firm, Luxembourg, (Luxembourg)

Managed court cases records, prepared invoices, perform

legal procedures.

12.2015 - 01. 2016 **Administrative Officer**

CNS, Luxembourg, (Luxembourg)

Verified documents for reimbursement, maintained digital

databases, managed mail.

03.2013 - 06.2013**Corporate Officer**

DELAGARDELLE Law Firm, Strassen, (Luxembourg)

Managed corporate documentation for incorporation of companies, organized board meeting, and drafted legal documents, assisted in the process related to the offering of

financial vehicles.

02.2012 - 03.2013Chargée d'étude dans le domaine Financier

CAYPHAS Law Firm, Luxembourg, (Luxembourg)

Annual statements, corporate accounting. Electronic filing

before the Trade Register of annual accounts.